So the cakes are coming on.
If you have a look here, you'll notice we've now got a nine cakes.
Our three by three.
We're trying to imitate this site here.
Uh, again you can choose a size.
We've just made it a bit bigger because we're not going to do this whole sign thing here, which obviously
you could, uh, we're just trying to make it more visually appealing.
So we've got our header and we've got our nine cakes.
So, um, this is how it looks at the moment.
So essentially we've got our header image which is at the top here.
And we've got our table with three rows row one, row two and row three.
And in each row we've got three columns with our different cakes in there.
They've got our different names.
Um, but what we need is just to make this a little bit more interesting.
What do you think we need, Josh?
I think we need the names of our cakes.
Come up with some ideas of what we're going to call, uh, individual cakes.
And also, we need a background.
Yeah, that would be good.
Start looking.
Okay, so we want to put a little bit of text.
I mean you see here each of these has got something written beneath the cake.
What it's called.
Uh, so we need to put a bit of text beneath these cakes and yeah, maybe a little background just to
add a little bit of something to this.
So let's, uh, get some text beneath these cakes.
Okay.
So we've got our, we've got our tables all set up for us.
So all we need to do is you can see we've got our, uh, TD here.
Um, so this is basically where we've got our cake image and everything.
So inside of that TD we are going to put some text.
So this is our first one.
Hey what is that.
Looks like a carrot cake or something.
Yeah.
Carrot cake.
That's moist.
Um uh yeah.
So um strawberry.
And save that before we do, let's just make it a paragraph.
So just p so that's going to make sure it just stays nicely together.
So moist carrot cake now and refresh.
Ah moist carrot cake.
Yes.
But it needs uh it looks irritating.
Like it I think it's got to be put on the, on the side there.
What do you think we got into that?
Yeah, I think we should.
Center.
Okay.
So center.
Center.
And we just put that like so.
And let's take a squeezy of that.
All right.
So let's see that should be centered in the cell.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.
We also need some styling for this.
I definitely think, um, that we should have something because alone it just, I say we need like a
H3 or something for this.
An H3 on that we can look we can always change.
So we start with H3.
Um, we go here, let's just take that and we'll put it over there.
Now we save that and let's see it's a little bit better.
Yeah I think that's looking a little bit better okay.
So you see you really can fiddle around however you like so you can act.
You can do whatever you like.
Okay.
So assuming that's what we want, we're going to have to pick up a few little names for our other ones.
This is going to have to be repeated.
So so let's do a nice, easy way to repeat it.
So let's just take this out for now.
Um, let's just take this out.
Okay.
So now we can grab this whole section here, saving us a lot of time.
Copy it.
Come on.
See?
Yeah.
And now you with.
I showed you with this holding down command.
Hold down, command.
Hold it down.
Keep holding, keep holding.
Because we're going to put this in all these places.
So now and hit everything you hit happens in all those spaces.
Yeah.
So now we go one up the tab so we can be tabbed in.
So now we can paste paste.
And now we can type in.
Obviously what we type now is going to be the same would be the same for each one.
So we don't have moist carrot cake for all of them.
So now we have let go of the.
Yeah.
So no it'll keep it in.
Now as soon as we are not holding down command and we click down, it's gonna, it's just going to be
one deselected.
Now we're back to one.
So this was our moist carrot cake.
Uh, I am not sure what the what the names for all of our other ones are going to be.
We're going to have to come up with a whole range of creative names for our cakes.
So there's a crust there.
Right.
So here you can see he's fast as a speeding rat.
We have got all our cakes and everything from vanilla and chocolate to the whatever cake to the surprise
cake, to the moist cake, to the Christmas cake.
Whatever.
So not bad.
Um, so what we've managed to do is we've put in all of the cake details, put them all in at the moment.
But, um, we need a background, a background.
I mean, the whites a bit boring.
So how about putting.
So essentially what the background is, it's like an image that's going to sit behind all of this.
But as you scroll it sort of sits back there.
So how do you do that.
Okay.
So what we basically want is a background.
You either have a background that's very large and cover your whole area, but or you can have a background
that is smaller and HTML will automatically repeat repeat, repeat.
Um, that that image needs to be a repeatable image.
Okay.
So if you go to the finder we can see we've got this one.
But that is not going to repeat very well.
That will be one that will just overlay on the whole thing.
Yeah.
So we'll use it later.
But at the moment that's not a great one for what we want to achieve here.
So we've got this now this is actually repeatable.
So it's like wallpaper.
You don't really notice if it's yeah if you notice a tiny bit obviously it's a cake's cut in but you'll
barely notice when it's been enlarged.
And there's the cake's covering it.
So you can actually search for images that are specifically made for this kind of stuff.
This image, I just I like the style of it.
So, um, we can add it in.
So in the body tag we've got here, which is our body we're going to put in background.
So this is basically telling us in the main body of our HTML there is going to be a background.
What's it going to be.
So it's simply background equals.
And then we've got our thing.
So if we go back to our file we can see what its name is a make sure you got that PNG command.
See the full name.
Now when you paste it in save it.
Now we've got a background.
So hit it refresh it.
Okay.
So you'll see.
Yeah you'll see.
Even if you had multiple rows that background image is just going to keep repeating a little bit noisy
now with many images.
So just be careful of that.
But you get the idea.
So obviously you want to look for one that's clean.
Depends on your website kind of look.
So with this one we would probably look for less.
We just want the people to be overwhelmed by cakes.
Yeah.
So much option so many options.
So that's basically how we're going to put in our background.
And, um, it's really starting to come on with all of these things we're adding in.
Right?
So there we have it.
Uh, we've got our website.
It's coming on.
And, uh, now what we need to do is because people can now browse our website and look at things,
um, remember this one when you go to a site and you could click, you see, as you move over something,
there come the little hand and it's like, ah, there is something I want to know.
How do you make out the black out?
We'll make this black out chocolate cake and up.
It's going to now pop with, you know, additional information.
So that's what we're missing at the moment.
You know there's nothing happening here.
All we've done so far is showed you how to create a one page website.
But how do you create an actual website that consists of more than one page that's coming up next?
So before you do it, you know what you've got to do.
Get your website, get some cakes, get your images stuck in there, add some descriptions, throw in
a background if you're keen on the background, and follow the story so that you are participating,
and we'll see you on the other side.